Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence, 14494
  - Roberts, Chuck, undated; 14587 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Robinson, Lisa, undated; 14586 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Romanski, M, undated; 14585 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Rose, Joel, undated; 14584 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Rosenthal, Laura, undated; 14583 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Rossi, Laura, undated; 14582 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Rower, Anne, undated; 14581 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Ruggiero, Gregg, undated; 14580 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Rugoff, Ralph, undated; 14579 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Rutkowski, Thaddeus, undated; 14578 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Salasin, Sal, undated; 14577 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Sand, Catherine, undated; 14576 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Sandiford, Frances, undated; 14575 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Sanger, Robyn, undated; 14574 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Savage, Tom, undated; 14573 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Sawry, Robert, undated; 14572 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Schain, Eliot, undated; 14571 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Schein, Lorraine, undated; 14570 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Schell, Marion, undated; 14569 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Schenler, Joan, undated; 14568 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Schiffrin, Anya, undated; 14567 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Schwartz, Leonard, undated; 14566 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Servin, Jacques, undated; 14565 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Shalom, undated; 14564 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Sherry, James, undated; 14563 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Shmaillo, Larissa, undated; 14562 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Siegle, Bob, undated; 14561 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Silverberg, Ira, undated; 14560 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Silverman, Hersch, undated; 14559 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Sirowitz, Hal, undated; 14558 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Skiles, Don, undated; 14557 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Smith, Marla, undated; 14556 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Smith, Rod, undated; 14555 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Smith, Tracy, undated; 14554 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Sofeico, Henry, undated; 14553 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Sorel, undated; 14552 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Sorrentino, Gilbert, undated; 14551 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Sparrow, undated; 14550 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Spielberg, Peter, undated; 14549 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Spodarek, Diane, undated; 14548 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Stauffer, Jill, undated; 14547 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Stefan-Cole, Janyce, undated; 14546 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Stettner, Irving, undated; 14545 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Strausbaugh, John, undated; 14544 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Strickland, Stephanie, undated; 14543 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Sukenick, Ron, undated; 14542 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Susler, Betsy, undated; 14541 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Swanberg, Ingrid, undated; 14540 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Swezey, Ken, undated; 14539 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Taylor, Cathy, undated; 14538 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Taylor, Claude, undated; 14537 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Teags, Debi, undated; 14536 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Thornton, Thomas, undated; 14535 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Tillman, Lynne, undated; 14534 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Tilson, Charlotte, undated; 14533 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Tilson, Jake, undated; 14532 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Tisa, Ken, undated; 14531 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Tobin, Juanita, undated; 14530 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Topp, Mike, undated; 14529 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Trask, Jason, undated; 14528 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Ulin, David, undated; 14527 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Underwood, John, undated; 14526 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Urdang, Stephanie, undated; 14525 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Versace, Nathan, undated; 14524 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Violi, Paul, undated; 14523 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Vitale, Alfred, undated; 14522 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Waldman, Anne, undated; 14521 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Warshawski, Morrie, undated; 14520 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Watson, Carl, undated; 14519 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Weber, Ben, undated; 14518 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Weber, Bruce, undated; 14517 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Wellman, Jerry, undated; 14516 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Whittemore, Reed, undated; 14515 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Wierzbicki, Carol, undated; 14514 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Williams, Gary, undated; 14513 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Williams, Jonathan, undated; 14512 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Wilmarth, Richard, undated; 14511 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Wilmott, Anne, undated; 14510 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Wilson, Blair, undated; 14509 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Wilson, Peter Lamborn, undated; 14508 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Wingate, Steve, undated; 14507 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Wittig, Bob, undated; 14506 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Witz, Bob, undated; 14505 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Wortsman, Peter, undated; 14504 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Wright, Jeff, undated; 14503 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Yourgrau, Barry, undated; 14502 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Zarco, Cyn, undated; 14501 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Zavatsky, Bill, undated; 14500 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Zelevansky, Paul, undated; 14499 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Zodd, undated; 14498 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Zukofsky, Paul, undated; 14497 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Zummer, Tom, undated; 14496 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; 14495 (Box 2, Folder 173)
- Series II: Manuscripts, 14274
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains manuscripts sent to Ron Kolm as a friend or as an editor. Included are many manuscript drafts by downtown writers.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by author.
  - Ahern, Tom--Manuscript Material for 5+5, undated; 14493 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, Holly--Lilly Lou, undated; 14491 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Alexander, Lynn, undated; 14492 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Andrucyk, Inez--"I've sold out.", undated; 14490 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Andrucyk, Inez--Blind Devotion, undated; 14489 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Anthony, William -- Artwork, undated; 14488 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bey, Hakim--What Is Moorish Anarchy?, undated; 14487 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Blagg, Max--Beaker Of Lightning, undated; 14486 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Blagg, Max--Bohemian Veneer, undated; 14485 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Blagg, Max--Bolham Butts, undated; 14484 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Blagg, Max--The Bump, undated; 14483 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Blagg, Max--Dad, undated; 14482 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Blagg, Max--Drinks And Towns In Notts & Yorks, undated; 14481 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Blagg, Max--Five Days, undated; 14480 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Blagg, Max-- Forgive Me Hollywood, undated; 14479 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Blagg, Max--Fresh Welts, undated; 14478 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Blagg, Max--Gush, undated; 14477 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Blagg, Max--It's Time, undated; 14476 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Blagg, Max--Last Of London, undated; 14475 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Blagg, Max--Maracas, undated; 14474 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Blagg, Max--Monkey Wrench In The Garden Of Allah, undated; 14473 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Blagg, Max-- The Origins of Dance, undated; 14472 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Blagg, Max--Poldrick's Little Secret, undated; 14471 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Blagg, Max--3 Locations/Notations From The Trek, undated; 14470 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Blagg, Max--What Remains, undated; 14469 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Burroughs, William--Some Considerations On The Paperback Publication of The Necronomicon, undated; 14468 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Carter, Michael--Artist's Call, undated; 14467 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Carter, Michael--Nigredo, undated; 14466 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Carter, Michael--20 Years, undated; 14465 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Cherches, Peter--The Music Critic And The Soprano, undated; 14464 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Deyab, Larry--Artwork, undated; 14463 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Duhamel, Denise--Why The Gap Should Have Picked Me Instead Of Max Blagg For It's Television Poetry Commercial, undated; 14462 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Eidus, Janice--The Mail, undated; 14461 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Eidus, Janice--The Marriage Breakfast, undated; 14460 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Eidus, Janice--Out Of The Schoolyard, undated; 14459 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Feast, Jim-- Authors Intros (Part XIII a-c), undated; 14458 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Feast, Jim-- Autonomedia Proposal, undated; 14457 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Feast, Jim--Beat Seminar Chronology, undated; 14456 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Feast, Jim--Chagunas, undated; 14455 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Feast, Jim--Chants For Seance, undated; 14454 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Feast, Jim--Con Lady and the Unknown Gangster, undated; 14453 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Feast, Jim--Day Of Infamy, undated; 14452 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Feast, Jim--Guns & Gonads: A Secret History of the O.J. Jury, undated; 14451 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Feast, Jim -- Lundi, Vendredi, undated; 14450 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Feast, Jim--Madison/Pulaski, undated; 14449 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Feast, Jim--Ming Sing, undated; 14448 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Feast, Jim--One Size Fits All Party Platform, undated; 14447 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Feast, Jim--On Pataphysics, undated; 14446 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Feast, Jim--Untitled, undated; 14445 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Feast, Jim--Vowel, undated; 14444 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Filzman, Norman--The Catering Wall, undated; 14443 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Fishberg, Lawrence--First Person, undated; 14442 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Fishberg, Lawrence--The Rubber Room, undated; 14441 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Golden, Mike--A Downtown State Of Mind, undated; 14440 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Golden, Mike--Pitch This, undated; 14439 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Golden, Mike--Please Don't Squeeze The Shaman, undated; 14438 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Golden, Mike--Rope Dancing In Little Egypt, undated; 14437 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Golden, Mike -- Miscellaneous Manuscripts, undated; 14436 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Golden, Mike--Without Daring, undated; 14435 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Hageman, Leita--Poems, undated; 14434 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Heine, Dean--The Frog Poem, undated; 14433 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Halgren, Will--To The Tune Of Miss Lulu Had A Steamboat, undated; 14432 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Hamill, Juan--The Big Sleep, undated; 14431 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Hardin, Rob-- Erased Mistress, undated; 14430 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Hardin, Rob--Evolution, undated; 14429 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Hardin, Rob--First Draft, undated; 14428 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Hardin, Rob--Hugo Wolf, undated; 14427 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Hardin, Rob--Inquiry, undated; 14426 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Hardin, Rob--Mood Music, undated; 14425 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Hardin, Rob--Senryu, undated; 14424 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Hardin, Rob--Tomomania, 260578 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Holman, Bob--Epithalamium, undated; 14423 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Holman, Bob--Fire: Friend Or Foe?, undated; 14422 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Holman, Bob--For Jorge Brandon, undated; 14421 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Holman, Bob--If I Were To Throw My Money, undated; 14420 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Holman, Bob--Not For Lack Of Understanding, undated; 14419 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Huberman, David--Bacon And Blintzes, undated; 14418 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Huberman, David--Call Me Killer, undated; 14417 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Huberman, David--Fat Boy, undated; 14416 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Huberman, David--The Grind, undated; 14415 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Huberman, David--Hard-up, Hard-on, Limp Dick, 260579 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Huberman, David--Life Sentence, undated; 14414 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Huberman, David--Nuclear Age Boy, undated; 14413 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Huberman, David--Psycho T.V. Shows, undated; 14412 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Huberman, David--She's The One, undated; 14411 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Huberman, David--Talk About It, undated; 14410 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Huberman, David--Word Man, undated; 14409 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Kasper, Michael--Words With Pictures, undated; 14408 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Kolm, Ron/TZ--Beach Party, undated; 14407 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Kolm, Ron--Death In Koln, undated; 14406 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Kolm, Ron--Fronts, undated; 14405 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Kolm, Ron--In The Silence Between Bombs, undated; 14404 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Kolm, Ron/Zummer, Tom--Duke & Jill Postmodernism Parody, undated; 14403 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Kolm, Ron--Make Love, Not War, undated; 14402 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Kolm, Ron--Meet Me At Mao's, undated; 14401 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Kolm, Ron--My Father, undated; 14400 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Kolm, Ron--The Scholar, undated; 14399 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Kolm, Ron--Suburban Ambush, undated; 14398 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Kolm, Ron--Swimming At The Shallow End Of The Pool, undated; 14397 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Kolm, Ron--The Vision, undated; 14396 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard--The Literature Of Soho, undated; 14395 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard--Blowing The College Teaching Biz, undated; 14394 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli--Manuscripts, undated; 14393 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Kruth, John--"probably bob", undated; 14392 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Kruth, John--The Mysterious History Of Manhattan, undated; 14391 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - LaBombarda, Michael--Plays, undated; 14390 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - LaBombarda, Michael--Poetry, undated; 14389 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - LaBombarda, Michael--Prose, undated; 14388 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Leary, Mary--Trash Can Trolls, undated; 14387 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Leary, Mary--Who In The Hell Is Frandon Freels?, undated; 14386 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Leary, Mary--Miscellaneous Manuscripts, undated; 14385 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Litzsky Tsaurah-Fallout Follies, undated; 14384 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Litzsky Tsaurah--Sex, Sex, Sex, undated; 14383 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Litzsky, Tsaurah--The End Of The World, undated; 14382 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Litzsky, Tsaurah--Three Poems, undated; 14381 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Mathews, Harry and others--"Oulipo" material, undated; 14380 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Maynard, Joe--Clancy's, 260580 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Maynard, Joe--Manuscripts, undated; 14379 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - McGlynn, Bob--N, undated; 14378 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Myles, Eileen--December, undated; 14377 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Nostrand, Jennifer--Untitled Poetry Manuscripts, undated; 14376 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Ochiishi--In From The Dream, undated; 14375 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Padua, Jose--Manuscripts, undated; 14374 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Barbie & Her Perilous Anatomy, undated; 14373 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Plantenga, Bart--The Beer Mystic's Shadow, undated; 14372 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Big Nouns, Unconjugated Verbs, undated; 14371 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Beliefs In The Material Progress, undated; 14370 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Cold Crackpot Life, undated; 14369 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Confessions Of A Beer Mystic, undated; 14368 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Enchanting Bonbons, undated; 14367 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Fellow De Se, undated; 14366 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Floating Flowers, undated; 14365 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Fun=Disney+Balanced Checkbook+BMW-Gum Disease, undated; 14364 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Get Or Be Gotten, undated; 14363 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Hitler's Dog, undated; 14362 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Plantenga, Bart--I Don't Feel Like Myself & I Feel Good, undated; 14361 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Interdiction, undated; 14360 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Duke & Jill Parody --Duke & Jill Run Out Of Coffee, undated; 14359 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Randall, Michael--Buzzard Hunting Dog, undated; 14358 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Randall, Michael--A Dollar's Worth, undated; 14357 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Randall, Michael--Eight Ball, undated; 14356 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Randall, Michael--Geronimo, undated; 14355 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Randall, Michael--Ice, undated; 14354 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Randall, Michael--Joey, undated; 14353 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Randall, Michael--A Man Wrapped In Plastic, undated; 14352 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Randall, Michael--Maneuvers, undated; 14351 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Randall, Michael--October Music, undated; 14350 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Randall, Michael-- Sex And Temperament In Three Primitive Societies, undated; 14349 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Randall, Michael--Miscellaneous Poems, undated; 14348 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Rapaport, Jill--Bellevue, undated; 14347 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Rapaport, Jill--Death, undated; 14346 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Rapaport, Jill--H.R. Haldeman, 1993, Which Seems To Mean Something, 14345 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Rapaport, Jill--Hong Kong Song, undated; 14344 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Rapaport, Jill--Panoplistic Traditions In Memphis, undated; 14343 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Rapaport, Jill--The Scintillation Of The Soviet Interstice, undated; 14342 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Rapaport, Jill--The Weirdness Of The Text, undated; 14341 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Rattray, David--The Butterfly, undated; 14340 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Rutkowski, Thad--Manuscripts, undated; 14339 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Salasin, Sal--Gary Gilmore--"Nothing to prove", undated; 14338 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Savage, Tom--A Good Friday, undated; 14337 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Savage, Tom-- Anecdotal Ticket For Saving Lost Souls, undated; 14336 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Savage, Tom--The Assassination Of Jesse Helms, undated; 14335 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Savage, Tom--Between B & C There's A Piano, undated; 14334 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Savage, Tom--"Bunker" poems, undated; 14333 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Savage, Tom--Collaborations (w. Bill Kushner & Dean Kostos), undated; 14332 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Savage, Tom--Computer Set Up Fantasy, undated; 14331 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Savage, Tom--Creating The Whites In Their Eyes, undated; 14330 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Savage, Tom--Enemies, undated; 14329 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Savage, Tom--First Fidelity, Here's What We See, undated; 14328 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Savage, Tom--Hypnagogia, undated; 14327 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Savage, Tom--Impatience, undated; 14326 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Savage, Tom--"It was such fun having nutmeg over you", undated; 14325 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Savage, Tom--July 4, 1991, 14324 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Savage, Tom--Just Say Ouch, undated; 14323 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Savage, Tom--More Noise, undated; 14322 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Savage, Tom--Plodding Through Posterity At Fales, undated; 14321 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Savage, Tom--Poetry By The Pound?, undated; 14320 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Savage, Tom--Prove That I Lie, undated; 14319 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Savage, Tom--Selling Books On The Street, undated; 14318 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Savage, Tom--Shop Talk At Word Station Twelve, undated; 14317 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Savage, Tom--There's No Way Outta Here, undated; 14316 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Savage, Tom--Tompkins Square Tree Talk, undated; 14315 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Savage, Tom--Train West Of Sardou & Sapho, undated; 14314 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Savage, Tom--Unsafe Sex, undated; 14313 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Savage, Tom--Wildfires Burn In My Heart, undated; 14312 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Schein, Lorraine--Clitoral, or The Ninth Orgasm, undated; 14311 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Schein, Lorraine--Sex, undated; 14310 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Schiffrin, Anya--Articles, undated; 14309 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Scutti, Susan--Economics, undated; 14308 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Sirowitz, Hal-- Untitled book-length manuscript, undated; 14307 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Sirowitz, Hal--Miscellaneous manuscripts, undated; 14306 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Sirowitz, Hal--Collaborations with Blair Wilson, undated; 14305 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Sparrow--Manuscripts, undated; 14304 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Sparrow--Against Nature, undated; 14303 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Sparrow--Appearances manuscript, undated; 14302 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Sparrow--Cartoons, undated; 14301 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Sparrow--One Size Fits All, undated; 14300 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Sparrow--Presidential Campaign, undated; 14299 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Taylor, Claude--Manuscripts, undated; 14297 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Topp, Mike--Bohemian Rhapsody, undated; 14296 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Topp, Mike--The Disappointment, undated; 14295 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Topp, Mike--Red Dust manuscript, undated; 14294 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Topp, Mike--Miscellaneous poems, undated; 14293 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Topp, Mike--Book manuscript (w. poem dedicated to Topp by Paul Violi), undated; 14292 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Ulin, David--Miscellaneous manuscripts, undated; 14291 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Vitale, Alfred--Miscellaneous manuscripts, undated; 14290 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Vitale, Alfred -- Six Sex Poems For An Erotic New York, undated; 14289 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Watson, Carl--Barndance In The Galleries Of Sodom, undated; 14288 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Watson, Carl--Mechanical Humanism, undated; 14287 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Watson, Carl--Modern Love As A Function Of Myth, undated; 14286 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Watson, Carl--Swirling Water In The Brain Causes Madness, undated; 14285 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Wierzbicki, Carol -- Untitled, undated; 14284 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Witz, Bob--"Materials", undated; 14283 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Witz, Bob--Untitled, undated; 14282 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Witz, Bob-- Miscellaneous Manuscripts, undated; 14281 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Zummer, Thomas--(Excerpts from Landscapes), undated; 14280 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Zummer, Thomas--The Library of Secrets, undated; 14279 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Zummer, Thomas--Three Films and Two Optical Devices I Will Never Make, undated; 14278 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Zummer, Thomas--The Unbearable Likeness Of Being, undated; 14277 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Zummer, Thomas--Video Furta Sacra, undated; 14276 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Miscellaneous Manuscripts, undated; 14275 (Box 4, Folder 91)
- Series III: The Unbearables, 14224
  This series contains materials relating to the various events, readings, and periodical publications of The Unbearables; artwork and manuscripts relating to the publication of The Crimes of the Beats; and artwork and manuscripts relating to the publication of Help Yourself.
  - Miscellaneous Unbearables, undated; 14273 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Readings -- Chez Rollo, undated; 14272 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Sparrow Big Fish "Between The Bombs" Event, undated; 14271 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Initiation Proceedings -- No Bar, undated; 14270 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - First Crimes Of The Beats Reading At No Bar, undated; 14269 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Unbearables Corpse, undated; 14268 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Reading At Fez Under Time Cafe, undated; 14267 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Second Reading At Fez Under Time Cafe, undated; 14266 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Third Crimes Of The Beats Reading, undated; 14265 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Second NYU Beat Protest, June 1995, 14264 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Impeachment Proceedings At Eureka Joe's, undated; 14263 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Sophisticated Unbearables Reading, Ward-Nasse, undated; 14262 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Famous Writers Seance, undated; 14261 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Readings --Shandon Star, undated; 14260 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Life Cafe Readings (1st Series), undated; 14259 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Night of 1000 Sponsors, undated; 14258 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - At The Poetry Project, undated; 14257 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Endangered Species Reading, undated; 14256 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Digitas, undated; 14255 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Nuyorican Style Reading At Biblio's, undated; 14254 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Miscellaneous Flyers, undated; 14253 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - New Yorker Protest #1, undated; 14252 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - New Yorker Protest #2, undated; 14251 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - First Brooklyn Bridge Reading, 1994, 14250 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Reading #2, undated; 14249 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Utopia Reading, undated; 14248 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Deconstructing The University Symposium, 1996, 14247 (Box 4, Folder 118)